<!-- This file represents the description data of GPS One Fix Collection GUI fields. -->
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>


<TERMS>

   <TERM>App Tracking</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION><![CDATA[
   Collect a series of Position Reports using one single iteration of device setup and tear down (see Single Shot).  <br />
   In other words: [Initialize] + [Register] + [Activate] + [Fix 1] + [Fix 2] + ... + [Fix N] + [De-Activate] + [Unregister] + [Release].
   ]]>
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Number of Fixes </TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION> 
   Number of App Tracking Fixes to trigger and collect
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Secs Between Fixes</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION>
   Time interval in seconds to wait before starting a new app tracking position request
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Wait For Events Completion</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION>
   Indicates if QXDM should wait for session completion events as readiness for the next position request<br />
   If checked, user should also specify how long to wait.
   This option is designed to help achieve the 1 fix per second requirement in a test collect.
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Single Shot</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION><![CDATA[
   Collect a series of Position Reports where each session is wrapped with device setup and tear down (see App Tracking).  <br />
   In other words: <br />
   [Initialize] + [Register] + [Activate] + [Fix 1] + [De-Activate] + [Unregister] + [Release] <br />
   [Initialize] + [Register] + [Activate] + [Fix 2] + [De-Activate] + [Unregister] + [Release] <br />
   : <br />
   [Initialize] + [Register] + [Activate] + [Fix N] + [De-Activate] + [Unregister] + [Release] <br />
   ]]>
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Number of Sessions</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION> 
   Number of Single Shot Fixes to trigger and collect
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Secs Between Sessions</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION> 
   Time interval in seconds to wait before starting a new single shot position request
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>E911 (Control Plane)</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION> 
   Indicates if the single shot collect should be done as a series of Emergency 911 dialed calls that results in control plane position requests
   </DESCRIPTION>
   
   <TERM>Call String</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION> 
   The numerical digits to dial on the handset for triggering an E911 position request
   </DESCRIPTION>
  
   <TERM>Call Duration</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION> 
   The interval in seconds of the E911 call for each control plane position session
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Call Type</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION> 
   Pull down menu allowing user to specify to make GSM or WCDMA E911 calls
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Full Phone Setup</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION><![CDATA[
   Indicates whether each E911 call session should be wrapped by device setup and tear down. <br />
   In other words: <br />
   [Initialize] + [Register] + [Activate] + [Call 1] + [De-Activate] + [Unregister] + [Release] <br />
   [Initialize] + [Register] + [Activate] + [Call 2] + [De-Activate] + [Unregister] + [Release] <br />
   : <br />
   [Initialize] + [Register] + [Activate] + [Call N] + [De-Activate] + [Unregister] + [Release] <br />
   If unchecked, the test becomes: <br />
   [Initialize] + [Register] + [Activate] + [Call 1] + [Call 2] + ... + [Call N] + [De-Activate] + [Unregister] + [Release].   
   ]]>
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Error Handling</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION> 
   Indicates whether QXDM should continue with the collect run or terminate immeditely, upon encountering an error condition.
   If user chooses to keep going with the collect run, then when error is encountered, QXDM will make a best-effort to recover and continue.
   This best effort "recovery" may require a device re-registration cycle.
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Quality of Service Accuracy</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION> 
   Species the accuracy threshold (in meters) for MS-based position session in the session start diagnostic command
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Fix Mode</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION> <![CDATA[
   Pull-down menu to specify collect type to trigger va the session start diagnostic command:  <br />
	  Standalone,<br />
	  MS-Based,<br />
	  MS-Assisted,<br />
	  Optimal Speed,<br />
	  Optimal Accuracy,<br />
	  Optimal Data
	  ]]>
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Handset Start State</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION><![CDATA[
   Radio buttons to define the initial state of the handset, with respect to GPS assistance data. <br />
   Custom : allow user to select the assistance data set to clean before starting GPS sessions <br />
   Reset : mimics a phone reset, where all assistance data will be deleted <br />
   Cold : mimics a cold start, where all assistance data besides almanac will be deleted <br />
   Warm : mimics a warm start, where only ephemeris will be deleted <br />
   Hot : mimics a hot start, where nothing will be deleted <br />
   XTRA-cold : mimics a cold start with XTRA feature enabled, where a selected set of assistance data will be deleted
   ]]>
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Client Type</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION><![CDATA[ 
Specifies the client type to be used during the initialization step of the handset setup. <br />
Values allowed include: <br />
0 PDSM_CLIENT_TYPE_BROWSER<br />
1 PDSM_CLIENT_TYPE_UI<br />
2 PDSM_CLIENT_TYPE_PDA<br />
3 PDSM_CLIENT_TYPE_DM<br />
4 PDSM_CLIENT_TYPE_NI<br />
5 PDSM_CLIENT_TYPE_BREW<br />
6 PDSM_CLIENT_TYPE_JAVA<br />
7 PDSM_CLIENT_TYPE_TEST<br />
8 PDSM_CLIENT_TYPE_TEST2<br />
9 PDSM_CLIENT_TYPE_OEM
   ]]>
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Server Configuration Parameter Source</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION><![CDATA[ 
   Pull down menu to specify how QXDM will find the location of Positition Determination server, if needed<br />
   Use NV Default - QXDM will read the location from NV Items on the handset
   Use Custom Local Options - User will specify on the GUI
   ]]>   
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Server Configuration Custom IP</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION>
   IP Address of the Position Determination server for users who chooses customer options
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Server Configuration Custom Port</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION>
   IP Port of the Position Determination server for users who chooses customer options
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Reference Position</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION>
   Allows user to specify static reference (truth) position (latitude, longitude, and altitude, in degrees, degrees, and meters, respectively) that will be used during the summary CSV generation (if enabled).
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Start GPS</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION>
   After all the configurations have been set up, click this button to kick off the GPS collection run
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Stop GPS</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION>
   While a GPS collection run is in progress, click this button to stop it before completion.
   User will likely need to reset the handset before the next run.
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Reset</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION>
   Click this button to restore the GUI configurations back to default values
   </DESCRIPTION>

   <TERM>Write To File</TERM>
   <DESCRIPTION>
   Check this box to enable generation of a summary CSV containing the position reports observed during the collection run.
   Note that this option is not recommended for App Tracking run where events wait is disabled.
   </DESCRIPTION>

</TERMS>

